계속 보자면, 그다음 조항들도 활성화됐어
Now, to review, the following provisions are hereby activated:
냉장고를 보면 2개의 개인 선반과 1개의 공용 선반이 있었는데
In the refrigerator,
이제는 셋이서 각자의 선반을 쓰고
the three of us now get individual shelves
냉장고 문이 공용이야
and the door becomes communal.
아파트 청소는 일주일에 두 번에서 세 번으로 늘어날 거야
Next, apartment vacuuming shall be increased from two to three times a week
죽는 피부 세포들이 쌓이는 속도에 맞춰야지
to accommodate the increased accumulation of dead skin cells.
세 번째로 화장실 시간인데
Third, the bathroom schedule.
여자들은 다른 요구도 있다고 알고 있으니까 그에 대해서는 의논해봐야겠어
I'm given to understand women have different needs, so, we'll have to discuss that.
난 잘래
I'm going to bed.
일단 이건 들고 가
At least take this with you.